Previously on Sons of Anarchy...
Dear Mo, I'm so lost here in Charming.
The Club, my family, everyone is a stranger.
I see my best friend and my wife
grown closer and closer.
I feel nothing, not even fear.
- I'll hand-deliver Jimmy O'Phelan.
- What do you want?
My son, my mother and my club.
And I'm supposed to just trust you, huh?
Hey, my club finds out, I'm dead.
It's Gemma's statement about what happened
with Polly and Edmond at the safe house.
If you want her clear of the homicide,
get her on board.
This is from Stahl, isn't it?
Do not get in bed with this bitch.
I am telling you.
This is what you need to do to protect SAMCRO.
Kill the deal,
or I'll turn my self in to the U.S. Attorney
and tell him my statement...
was a pack of lies you fed me.
I'm sure that agent...
you're hanging all the blame on,
will have no problem backing me up on that.
We know, that Jimmy has reached out to
the Russians in Northern California.
The ones we've been muling your handguns to?
Aye. You need to kill him.
Before he exiles some place
where we can't find him.
Comes with rewards.
We're willing to significantly
expand your gun business.
Former high ranking leaders of the IRA...
now make up the ruling
council of the Real IRA.
Did you have any contact
with any of these guys?
The Irish gave Jimmy save passage out of Belfast.
In exchange for my kid.
He's up north with the Russians.
- Putlova?
- Yeah.
I need you to tell me what's going on with Stahl.
You just gonna have to trust me.
I can't protect you from Clay if he finds out,
and if you go to jail
with them knowing you're a rat,
you'll be dead in a day.
Hey.
Morning.
I love you.
I love you too, son.
You don't know that.
I have a feeling.
What?
Whatever happens today,
I'm right here.
I know.
I got something for you.
It may be a wee bit small, by now.
All right.
- I'm so happy for you, man.
- Thank you.
Hey,
Lyla's got something she wants to say.
We're getting married.
- Yeah, brother.
- Thanks.
That's a party.
- The best change I can wished.
- I know.
- Yeah.
- Hi.
Yeah.
- To Ope and Lyla.
- Sons!
Hooray!
Baby?
Hey.
I'm looking for you.
Yeah, I'm just cleaning up.
- Gotta go and see Otto.
- All right.
I'll call the Indians.
Wheres the pick-up?
I wouldn't go in there.
Sit for a sec.
What's going on?
Today's about to go off the rails, baby.
We got to find Jimmy before we go inside.
I know what you have to do.
This is more than retaliation.
We made a deal...
with the irish kings.
Taking out Jimmy gets us access to
a much higher level of merchandise.
- What irish kings?
- Real IRA council.
Same guys got us the deal
to get Abel back from Jimmy.
Redheaded godfathers.
You do not say no to these guys.
Hey,
this is good for us, baby.
I don’t have that many more years
to add at that table.
This is an opportunity for us to finish big.
Set us up for the rest of our lives.
While we're sittin' in a cell.
We don't know how any of that
shit is gonna shake out.
Let's not worry about that right now.
You're right.
I'll worry about it tomorrow.
When they carted us both of to jail.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
~ SubCentral.de präsentiert ~
~ Staffel 3, Episode 13 ~
~ " NS " ~
~ Transcript ~
~ zerotollerance ~
~ Syncro ~
~ The Hellraiser ~
~ für www.SubCentral.de ~
- This is excellent work.
- Yes, I know.
I'm finishing out here arrangements
in Santa Caterina.
- Funds should transfer this afternoon.
- Good.
Donny's closing things up around here.
He'll be back in a couple of hours.
Maybe we should try and
get a flight down tonight, yeah?
- I'll set it up.
- Grand.
Tig, can I show you something?
- It could be really important for you guys.
- Later.
Hey.
- Mine and my pop's.
- Okay. KG-9's.
We've got to call in to Lin for the other one.
- I'm at the station when you need me.
- Oh, you're the best,
Chemo-Sabi.
- That ain't funny.
- Yes, it is.
What are you doing?
I'm gonna turn my self in.
- What are you talking about?
- Drive.
- Gemma, I...
- Drive!
Yeah, Lenny is really tagged
with the gulag crew in here.
It's, uh... Putlova's muscle.
We need a location today.
I might be able to get a few minutes
with him at the fence, but...
it ain't gonna be easy.
We're trying to arrange whatever
we can on our end.
Yeah. Okay.
You're doing okay, bro?
Yeah.
Where is the case at?
I'm not really sure, my...
my P.D. don't speak real good english.
P.D.? Wh...
What are you doing with a public defender?
We've put Rosen and Lowen on it.
They had cameras in the reading room.
They got me offen the peckerwood on tape.
There's not much of a defense.
Are you gonna plea that down?
I got no brace in here, brother.
Apparently, I...
continued to exhibited pattern
of aggressive behavior.
I'll be...
I'll be on the road by the time
you guys are arraigned.
I'll...
I'll do what I can to get to Lenny, all right?
- Thank you.
- Bye, guys.
Do I need to post a chaperon,
or can you ladies
chat with some civility?
We'll be fine.
Good luck.
What's this?
It's my statement exonerating you from the
murder of Edmond Hayes.
And Polly's death has been
ruled self-defense, so...
you're cleared of the homicides.
Of course there is still the...
fleeing custody charge, but with your...
recent medical flare-up,
I got it decremented to house arrest.
You'll wear an ankle bracelet
for six months, and...
if you behave, you'll have it off in three.
I'll deny all of it.
So you would sacrifice your life in prison
just to undermine my case.
I found your folder.
I saw what Jax is giving you.
You are gonna get him killed.
If not by his own club,
then by the IRA.
You kill the deal,
or I'll tell the U.S. Attorney
it's all bullshit.
Well, unfortunately,
my testimony is already been documented.
So even if you wanted to take the fall,
it's to late.
Looks like you'll have to trust me.
You actually think that's possible, don't you?
You are a naive bitch.
These deals,
these relationships,
can never work.
And why is that?
Because they're based on lies.
You're lying to your bosses,
Jax is lying to his club,
you're both lying to each other.
There's no trust.
And something will go wrong.
Somebody will get hurt.
I promise you...
it'll end badly.
You're late.
Just came from your mother.
She's in the cage of Charming P.D.
She tried to turn herself in...
and shit on our deal.
Goddammed.
Doesn't matter.
She's been cleared of all the murder charges.
How?
Well,
Tyler confessed before she died.
Told me, everything that Gemma said
in her statement was true.
Jesus Christ.
It's one thing you bosses don't
know about our little deal,
but I got to think killing one of your own
might be a bad career move.
I didn't kill her.
Mexican bikers did.
Your mother seems to...
believe that you and I shouldn't...
trust each other.
She knows something I don't?
She thinks you're gonna get me killed.
Are you?
You boys are running out of time.
Bail hearing is set for tomorrow morning.
Clay is sitting down with Otto right now.
Hook him up with Lenny the pimp...
and we'll get some info.
The meeting has been arranged.
Good.
You owe me something now, don't you?
I remember Dooley, Brogan and Morph.
I never saw any of the others.
Put in the document along
with my statement...
about Jimmy and I'll sign off on the hole file.
Okay. Good.
Keep me on point to Jimmy.
Absolutely.
You're waiting for a tip, shithead?
How you're doing, Lenny?
- Better than you.
- Yeah.
It's a pretty solid majority these days.
No shit.
Listen, the...
club needs a big favor.
Need you to reach out to
your eastern bloc friends.
They're protecting an Ex-IRA.
Jimmy O'Phelan.
Either in northern Cali or up in Oregon.
Why do you want Jimmy?
Killed five members in Northern Ireland.
We...
We need the location on the safehouse.
Putlova has got no love for the irish.
I'm sure he'll be open to better offer.
Buy him out?
That's the only we to get Jimmy.
All right. Once you...
Once you find out what that would look like,
we got to know fast, though.
I'll pass on what I know through the attorneys.
Okay, that'll work.
I'll let Clay know.
- You take care, Lenny.
- Okay, brother.
What a crap of shit.
Hey.
Where is she?
What were we just talking about?
I'm sorry, baby.
Nothing impulsive, right?
These are reckless times, Clay.
We are all doing impulsive things,
things that we would never do otherwise.
- I know.
- I don't think you do.
Losing Abel,
all the deaths...
Every decision you make...
has to be made in the light
of these extreme circumstances.
What are you saying?
It's a different time.
We can't look at Jax
in the same light as John.
Yeah. Okay.
Okay.
These equations were forwarded to me
by Lenny Janowitz's lawyer.
Don't know what it means.
Don't really want to.
20 equals zero. True.
38,358888...
minus 122,288818...
equals two million.
True or false?
Nice.
Give us a minute, will you?
We got to do the math.
Take a few, they're big numbers.
20 equals zero.
Lenny couldn't get a location.
The others are longitude and latitude.
Two million means we can buy Jimmy.
Two million, shit!
Why don't we just show up and take Jimmy?
We got enough hardware.
It's not gonna be the safehouse.
It's gonna be a place for the exchange.
Trust me, Putlova is bringing an army.
Yeah, looks like an access road
outside of Rio Vista.
40 minutes.
Ope.
Tell Lowen the equation is true.
Where the hell are we gonna get two million?
What, are we robbing banks now?
Tell Lenny's lawyer it's true.
Need a time.
You do know I charge hourly, right?
Just send it.
Jax, can I show you something?
Really important.
You really gonna want to know about it.
Not now, bro.
- You hear from Lenny?
- Yeah.
Putlova wants two million for Jimmy.
- Jesus Christ.
- Hey.
I need a minute.
- Where is Abel?
- Lyla and Neeta are with him at home.
Your mom is in jail.
I know. I heard.
The homicide charges were dropped.
She doesn't want Clay to know. She's...
terrified.
What's going on, Jax?
Please, you can tell me.
Jax!
Look!
- What's this?
- Go on.
After Tara got kidnapped,
I tried to tell you guys about this.
When I was on the counterfeit operation for Lin,
I was supposed to throw away all
the misprints and dirty runs.
I didn't.
This are three boxes full.
Twentys, fifties, hundreds.
Over five mil of fake currency.
Holy shit.
- Don't bend 'em.
- Come here, sit down.
I will lend you my hand
so that you can jerk yourself off.
- Come on. Take it.
- I accept that.
Don't you point that finger at me.
Put that away.
We got Eddy to loan us his print-cutter.
It's gonna take a couple of hours.
- All right.
- Everyone of these bills is irregular.
Any screw on them,
the Russians are gonna know.
Maybe we need to create
some sort of distraction.
Putlova is too smart.
I don't see how this is going down
without it turning bloody.
Well, than we better bring everybody.
Just in case it does.
If we can front-load the stacks with real cash,
could buy us enough time to
get Jimmy out of there.
Hey, I got 40 bucks in my wallet.
I got an idea.
Putlova wants two million for Jimmy.
Jesus Christ.
We got our hands on some counterfeit cash,
but I got to pet it out with real bills.
Buy us some time to get Jimmy out of there.
Where did you get the counterfeit cash?
Not your worry.
I need money.
I still have access to the 250k...
that we've used for Tara's ransome.
That should do it.
What happens when the club
asks you where you got it?
I'll tell 'em I was in evidence here.
That I got Unser to sign it on.
We're gonna be there.
- At the exchange.
- No.
If the Russians see you,
they will kill Jimmy.
If my club sees you,
they'll know someone ratted.
We can't take that risk.
It's the only way you get the cash.
I'll give you the location.
But you gotta hang back a few miles at least.
All right.
We'll put Jimmy in the van,
you send in your team,
pretend you're after the Russians.
Let us go, grab Jimmy.
Fair enough.
I'll set it up.
We've confirmed the charter flight
this afternoon from San Jose.
That's great.
That's wonderful.
Is Donny back yet?
No, I don't think so.
You're ready?
- Yeah.
- Two mil. More or less.
KG-9's, shotguns, mac-10.
Flag 'em up to you lads,
you're gonna need them.
You sure we can't spare one off the prospects?
We don't know what Putlova is gonna show up with.
We need bodies.
At least till we make the exchange.
Yeah, okay.
- Tara's here.
- Right on.
We keep you safe.
Yeah. Come on.
Okay.
I got it.
She's all set.
You sure about this?
I know that we can do it.
Admit it, you need me.
Yes, I do.
Need you to wear this.
Fancy.
I'm not gonna let anything happen to you.
To us.
Yeah.
Promise you'd tell me everything?
You'll know everything soon enough, babe.
Okay.
You guys headed out?
What gave it away?
Lowen is down at the station.
Finishing up Gemma's release.
She should be home soon.
Okay. Thanks.
- And I'm all set.
- Good.
You...
You stay hole.
Will do.
What you do for us?
It won't be forgotten.
- We're all set?
- Yeah, it's under it depth.
We make no mistakes.
Jackie boy.
You make it quick.
- You're good, old man.
- Take care of yourself, bro.
Yeah.
All right, bro. All right.
- Good luck, man.
- Yeah.
Let's go, boys.
Come on, let's move it.
When you got the text,
you'll let us know.
Then deliver these two letters.
I know. We'll handle it.
I love you, son.
I love you, too.
You're all right?
Yeah.
Let's just finish this.
No Donny?
Don't make sense.
Maybe he changed his mind.
Didn't Luke just up and leave you, too.
Luke didn't leave.
He got taken out.
Where we going?
We need to pick something up.
What the hell is this?
Sorry, Jimmy.
Jesus, Victor.
After all I've done for you?
The money, the guns?!
Don't do this.
Million per bag.
- 50 stacks, 20k in each.
- Thank you.
Moment.
Five more minutes and we're moving.
- We're good.
- Excellent.
Clay. Jackson.
Lovely to see you.
- Pleasure doing business with you.
- Yes.
Take care, gentlemen.
Viktor.
Tara, come here.
Almost done, Jimmy.
- Strict to the garage, okay?
- Absolutely.
- You're good?
- Go. Come on.
Where to?
It's fake.
Go! Get them!
Seems like Viktor has been
doing a little counting.
Here they come.
Close it up.
Yes, ma'am.
Let's go. Move.
Go, go, go!
Put out an APB on the Russians.
I want my money back.
I'm on it.
He's not here.
Shit!
- Where is he?
- Warm and cozy.
What the hell are you pulling, huh?
Just keeping us both honest.
You get Jimmy and my statement
when my club gets free of hard time.
My recommendation...
that the federal automatic weapons
charges will be reduced from...
15 to three years.
Parole in 14 months.
All that needs is my signature.
- Based on me turning over Luke?
- It's a sound record, yeah.
And for that...
you give me this.
Your statement of cooperation.
You'll show your full knowledge
of the gun running operation...
and any illegal activities perpetrated
by the irish council and Jimmy O'Phelan.
All that needs is your signature.
I sign this,
what's to stop you getting the IRA?
Let us rot in prison for 15 years?
What's to stop you...
from delivering this to your lawyer
and killing Jimmy?
Now, you...
just lied to me.
So it's your turn for
a show of good faith.
I'm officially a rat.
Your turn.
Where is Jimmy?
- Don't do this.
- Nothing changes.
I just need to see him alive
and then I sign it.
There is no play here.
Follow me.
- We're okay?
- I don't know.
Okay.
- Shit!
- Good afternoon.
Where's Jimmy O?
Okay, look, I can have a designation
here in 20 minutes...
and they'll shred this white trash shithole.
Get him.
Let's go.
My goddess for the american justice system.
Jimmy O'Phelan, you're being
taken into custody...
on suspicion of conspiracy,
committed terrorism and criminal acts.
Sorry things didn't work out he way
you planned, boys. Look at the irish though, yeah?
How'd you know he was here?
Guess your VP made a deal.
- Son of a bitch!
- Wait.
- What is she talking about?
- You made a deal for Jimmy?
What?
- I did it for the club.
- You rat!
- You're ratting!
- I got no choice!
- Look at the due that we're facing!
- All this time we've been tracking Jimmy,
you knew you gotta turn
him over to this bitch?
- He blew up five of our men!
- He was Chib's nephew.
I know! Sorry!
She made him do it. He really had no choice, Clay.
You hear me? You are dead!
Dead!
Go on.
You just signed my death warrant.
I'm sorry, but you know what?
Your mother was right.
This could have never worked.
There's just no trusts.
I had to make sure that the prince had turn rat.
Let's go.
Come on, people.
Jax, come here.
Arrest them.
Let's go.
The club will be out in three years,
if they don't kill anyone,
parole in 14 months.
- Make sure they're separate.
- All right.
Come on, sit down.
Down.
What's this idiot doing?
It's Unser.
Should I pull over?
He might know something.
Jesus Christ. Yeah, pull over.
What the hell is this, Wayne?
Sorry, I didn't have you cell number...
and I didn't wanna put this out
over the radio.
What?
I got an anonymous tip.
Propably bullshit.
But they said, that four or
five of Jimmys guys are...
gonna be waiting for you by the Newton turnout.
That's only a few miles south.
I can call the Sanwa Sheriffs
and have them check it out.
- No, I...
- Sheriffs are idiots. You guys check it out.
Wait. I don't wanna leave you alone.
I'll stay.
I'll call for backup.
- She'll be safe.
- Good.
It's okay. Go.
Really?
I got stage-3 cancer, sweetheart.
I ain't got that in my purse left.
No, thanks.
You should really have some.
You got to be shitting me.
What the hell is going on here?
Take care of our girls, Filip, yeah?
Oh, yeah.
This is insanity, Opie.
You have any idea what kind of
heat is this gonna bring to the club?
Put your hands on the wheel.
Please.
- Put your hands on the wheel.
- Please.
Please, don't do this.
Wait.
Please, Opie.
Please, you had mercy before.
I'm begging you.
Don't do this.
And now I don't.
This is what she felt.
Hey, let's go!
- Is that the deal?
- Yeah.
The left side.
I had rage work done on the right.
- Okay.
- Go ahead.
Let's go, kids.
"Dear Jackson, the truth about
your fahter is in these letters."
"You should know John like I did.
Maureen."
We need to see you.
Jax wanted you to read this.
Then burn it.
- What is it?
- I don't know.
Is Tara here?
No.
- She's at Jax's.
- Okay
Have a good night.
Hey, mom.
If you're reading this, that means
Stahl and Jimmy are dead.
And the club will be doing short time.
I'm sory it had to be this way, mom.
I know, how painful it's been for you, but...
I couldn't tell you.
We made you an accessory.
It was a club vote.
I'd never turn on my club or my family.
I'm not my father.
- I love you more than you could ever know.
- I'd do anything to be with you.
Every day...
it becomes more clear that I don't belong here.
I'm certain now that Clay and Gemma
are together.
They barely try to hide it from me.
Gemma hates my empathy.
She hates all of me.
Her show is terrifying.
I know my days are numbered, Mo.
And when these letters stop...
you can be certain that my death
will come at the hands of my wife...
and best friend.
At least my sweet Thomas
will never suffer my life.
I miss him so much.
I only pray that Jackson
finds a different path.
He already reminds me so much of myself.
~ für www.SubCentral.de ~
www.tvsubtitles.net